Stinky: Is it A, Gastropods, B, Marsupials or C, Planaria
迈克∶嗯...别帮我.
Ben: Um...don't help me, here.
臭虫∶我不会.
Stinky: I can't.
本∶嗯.那就选A,那个东西有汽.
Ben: Um...It's A, that thing with gas.
臭虫∶不是,选D,以上都不是.
Stinky: No, it's D, none of the above.
本∶但是你甚至没有说这个!
Ben: But you didn't even say that!
臭虫∶我认为不会选这个.
Stinky: I didn't think it was gonna be that.
本∶再问我另一个问题.
Ben: Ask me another question.
臭虫∶对还是错,有袋类动物用袋子来抱他们的孩子.
Stinky: True or false, Marsupials carry their young in pouches.
本∶肯定是错的.
Ben: Oh, that's gotta be false.
我是说这些动物去哪里买育儿袋呢?
I mean, where are these animals gonna buy pouches?
谁会卖育儿袋给它们?
And who's gonna sell 'em to 'em?
开萝尔∶是对的,本,你个小白痴!
Carol: It's true Ben, it's true, you little rodent!
本∶开萝尔,你打扰了我们!
Ben: Carol, you're interrupting!
开萝尔∶我情不自禁.我讨厌无知!
Carol: I can't help it.Ignorance nauseates me!
如果我以前没有跟你提过的话,
If I haven't mentioned it before, let me mention it now;
那我就现在告诉你,你真的让我失望透顶.
you're a real disappointment to me.
本∶你来这里就是为了取笑我?
Ben: Did you come in here just to bug me?
开萝尔∶对.
Carol: Yes.
臭虫∶不要因为她的话而沮丧.我家里的所有人都因为我和你混在一起,
Stinky: Don't let her get you down.
而对我失望了.
My whole family's disappointed in me for hanging out with you.
本∶再问我另一个问题.
Ben: Ask me another question.
臭虫∶怎么了?
Stinky: What's the point?
本∶问我问题,行吗!
Ben: Just ask me, OK!
臭虫∶本,放松,这个测试只占我们成绩的50%.
Stinky: Ben, relax, this test only counts for half our grade.
本∶臭虫,迄今为止,我的另外50%的成绩是一个D.
Ben: Stinky, so far the other half of our grade's a D.
臭虫∶对,就算最坏也是D负.
Stinky: Right, so the worst we can get is a D minus.
本∶哦,我们是在跟自己开玩笑.我们根本不可能会通过考试的.
Ben: Oh, we're kidding ourselves.There's no way we're gonna pass this exam.
臭虫∶那是你而已,我可都答对了.
Stinky: Speak for yourself, I haven't got a single question wrong.
本∶那是因为你是对着书做的.
Ben: That's because you got the book right in front of you.
麦琪∶本,开萝尔说你需要我的帮助.
Maggie: Ben, Carol says you need my help.
本∶不需要!妈妈,
Ben: I do not!Look Mom, the studying is coming along just fine.
你看,我们学的正好呢.事实上我刚才还在跟臭虫评论说学习是多么的有趣呢.
In fact I was just commenting to Stinky, how much fun learning is.
麦琪∶我希望如此.本,
Maggie: Well, I hope so, Ben; because if you bring home another D in Science,
you'll see another side of me, you've never seen before
臭虫∶有育儿袋吗?
Stinky: Does it have a pouch?
本∶妈妈,我们对这些东西了解的多好,
Ben: See Mom, we know this stuff so well,
我们还用这个来当笑话说呢.臭虫把你叫做有袋类动物.
we're already telling jokes about it.Stinky just called you a Gasiopod.
开萝尔∶有袋类动物!有袋类动物!
Carol: Marsupial!Marsupial!
本∶至少我们知道哪个动物有毁灭性,不是吗,开萝尔?
Ben: Well at least we know which animal has a blow whole, don't we, Carol?
本∶A!
Ben: A!
臭虫∶不是.
Stinky: No.
本∶B.
Ben: B.
臭虫:噢噢.
Stinky: Uh uh.
本∶C.
Ben: C.
臭虫∶错.
Stinky: Wrong.
本∶D.
Ben: D.
臭虫∶噢呼.
Stinky: Uh uh.
本∶一个都不对?
Ben: Well it's gotta be one of them.
臭虫∶脑筋急转弯.
Stinky: Trick question.
本∶我不要脑筋急转弯,我要简单一点的问题.
Ben: I don't need a trick question.I need an easy one.
臭虫∶今天是只有我一个没有穿胸罩还是劳拉林也没有穿?
Stinky: Was it just me, or was Laura-Lynn not wearing a bra today?
本:臭虫,这不是考试题.她穿了.
Ben: Stinky, that's not gonna be on the exam.And she was wearing a bra.
臭虫∶错.你连这个也回答错了.
Stinky: No.You got that wrong too.
威特∶唷伙计们!
Vito: Yo guys!
本:威特,不要告诉我你已经明天的考试你已经准备好了.
Ben: Vito, don't tell me you're already done studying for tomorrow's exam.
威特∶如果是说学习的话,那我决定说没有.
Vito: Well, I thought about studying and then I decided to just say no.
本∶那么,你怎么通过测试呢?
Ben: Well then, how are you gonna pass the test?
威特∶因为我有一个亲戚在复制室工作.
Vito: Well, let's just say I got a relative in the ditto room.
本∶你已经拿到我们的考试的答案!
Ben: You mean, you got the answers to our test!
威特∶嘘!本,我以为只有臭虫才会说这么愚蠢的话呢.
Vito: Shh!Ben, I'd expect Stinky to say something stupid like that.
臭虫∶你拿到我们考试的答案了!
Stinky: You got the answers to our test!
威特∶嘘!你们是想站在这里,
Vito: Shh!Do you wanna stand here and give this fool-proof plan away,
把事情都泄露出去,还是要和我一起分享这份答案呢?
or do you wanna share the wealth?
本∶但是我们可能会被老师抓住的!
Ben: But we could get caught!
臭虫∶我不能做这么冒险的事情,我父母不会喜欢我这样的.
Stinky: I can't risk that, my parents don't like me much as it is.
威特∶不,不,
Vito: No, no, it's perfect.There's nothing to get caught with.
You just memorise a few letters and you get an A
臭虫∶哇.
Stinky: Wow.
Vito: So do you wanna A, stay here and study and fail the test anyways
就只需要记住几个字母,然后就可以出去溜达,去紧身衣店铺,怎么样?
or B, memorise a few letters and go and hang out at the err...leotard shop?
本∶终于有一道我能做的多项选择题了.
Ben: Finally a multiple choice question I can handle.
威特∶好!好!
Vito: Alright!Yeah!
杰森∶对!
Stinky: Yeah!
本:明天见.迈克,你在做什么.
Ben: See you at the test tomorrow guys.Mike, what are you doing.
迈克∶我在和我的朋友们玩投篮.
Mike: I'm playing some hoops with my friends.
本:传过来,我要玩.
Ben: Pass it here, I'll play.
迈克∶不行,本,这可不是一个好主意
Mike: No, no, no.I don't think it'd be a good idea, Benny.
本:我看着女孩们试穿紧身衣三个小时,
Ben: I've been watching girls trying on leotards for three hours,
我已经锻炼过了.
I gotta exercise.
迈克∶妈妈和爸爸正在里面等你呢.他们生气了.
Mike: Mom and Dad are inside waiting for you and they are mad.
本∶对我生气?为什么?
Ben: At me?Why?
迈克∶我也知道的不错,不过好像是说你在学习时间偷跑出去了.
Mike: Well, I didn't here much,
but it was something about you were supposed to be studying and then you
skipped out.
本∶他们根本就不知道,
Ben: Ah, well, what they don't know is that I got this test covered from
我全都复习好了.
top to bottom, and they don't have a clue.
迈克∶你最好去跟他们解释清楚,
Mike: Well, you better go and explain that to them because they think
因为他们认为你敢溜走是因为你找到了一些作弊的诡计.
the reason you took off is because you found some fool-proof way to cheat.
本∶他们怎样知道这件事情呀?
Ben: How do they know these things?
迈克:本,是告诉你的时候了,爸爸妈妈是巫.
Mike: Well Benny, I think it's time you were told; Mom and Dad are witches.
本∶什么?
Ben: What?
迈克∶不会吧,不要跟我说你一点怀疑也没有.
Mike: Oh, come on, don't tell me you haven't suspected it.
你难道晚上的时候,从来都没有听见有很奇怪的声音从他们的房间里传出来吗.
I mean haven't you heard those strange noises coming from their room at night.
有时就算爸爸不在房间里的时候,也会有声音.
I mean and sometimes Dad's not even there!
本∶对.
Ben: Yeah.
迈克∶振作起来,本.
Mike: Snap out of it, Ben.
本,好了,
Benny, come on, the only reason they know you do this stuff is because
不逗你了,他们之所以知道这件事情是因为你根本就不是撒谎的料.
you're a slimy little kid.
本∶败露了,哼?
Ben: It shows, huh?
迈克∶本,他们了解你的每个行为,
Mike: Benny, look, just because they know every move you're gonna make,
所以根本就不可能不知道你的诡计.
there's no reason not to go through with this fool-proof plan of yours.
本∶是这样吗?
Ben: It isn't?
迈克∶当然.你死定了.
Mike: Of course it is.You're a walking dead man.
本∶但你跟我说...
Ben: But you just said...
迈克∶我知道我刚才所说的一切,做为你的哥哥,
Mike: I know what I just said, but Benny, I like messing with your mind;
捉弄你,就是其中的乐趣之一.好了,
it's one of the joys I have as your older brother.
我跟你出个主意,当你进到房间后,不要惊慌,
OK, now all things aside, when you go inside that house, don't panic,
装的酷一点,也不要露出破绽.
be very cool and don't crack.
本∶对!对!
Ben: Right!Right!
迈克∶好了,你可以的,弟弟.
Mike: Alright, you can do it bro.
本∶好,非常感谢,迈克.
Ben: Alright, thanks a lot, Mike.
迈克∶不要被一个事实吓倒,那就是他们在你还没有开始想之前,
Mike: And don't be throw by the fact that they know every thought in your
就知道你在想什么了.
head before you even think it.
本∶无以为报,迈克.
Ben: Thanks for nothing, Mike.
有了你的这些主意,我一定可以摆平妈妈和爸爸的.
And for your information, I can ha ndle Mom and Dad.
我会非常酷的.l.
I will be completely coo
杰森∶很好玩吧.
Jason: How interesting.
本∶哦,爸爸我只是...
Ben: Oh, Dad I just meant...
麦琪∶我只想知道你跟我说一件事情,
Maggie: The only thing I wanna hear from you young man is,
那就是什么哺乳动物把自己的孩子装在育儿袋里?
what do you call the mammal that carries its young in a pouch?
本∶幸运的.
Ben: Err...lucky.
开萝尔∶有袋类动物!有袋类动物!
Carol: Marsupial!Marsupial!
本∶开萝尔,你快让我完蛋了!
Ben: Carol, you're really starting to tick me off!
杰森∶如果我错了可以指出来;你正在开始激动起来.
Jason: Correct me if I'm wrong; you're starting to lose your cool.
本∶爸爸,我从未想过要作弊.
Ben: Dad, it never occurred to me to cheat.
麦琪∶如果你没有作弊的话,那你打算怎么通过考试呢?
Maggie: How do you expect to pass a test if you don't cheat?
本∶我...哈?
Ben: Well, I...Huh?
杰森∶本,你妈妈说的有道理.你现在是在严密的监视下,
Jason: Ben, your mom's right.
本,既然你没有学习,那么你唯一的希望就是作弊了.
Now you're under the gun here, Ben, and since you're
not studying, cheating's your only hope
本∶这样说来,我可以作弊!
Ben: So it's OK to cheat!
杰森∶不,作弊是不行的.
Jason: No, it is not OK to cheat.
本∶但你跟我说...
Ben: Well...But you just said...
杰森∶我知道我刚才说了什么,本.
Jason: I know what I said, Ben.We're messing with your mind.
作为你的父母,打乱你的思维也是其中的乐趣之一.
It's one of the only joys we have as parents.
麦琪∶本,整个学期你都没有好好的学过自然科学,
Maggie: Ben, you've been letting Science slide all semester and today,
而今天,在考试的前一天,你没有复习,
the day before the test you waste three hours doing God-knows-what!
却把时间浪费在做老天才知道的事情!我猜你是去看穿着紧身衣的女孩了.
My guess is, watching women in tight outfits.
本∶她真的是个巫婆.
Ben: She is a witch.
杰森∶你叫你妈妈什么来着?
Jason: What did you call your mother?
本∶什么也没有,什么也没有,什么也没有,对不起.
Ben: Nothing.Nothing, nothing, I'm sorry.
杰森∶好了,现在给你几个选择,
Jason: Alright, well here's your multiple choice, Ben.
本.A,
A, you can either stand here,
你可以继续站在这里,不停的说,
keep talking about it and get yourself in deeper or B,
you can go up to your room and study till you drop or C
或C,你也可以给我100万美元.
you can pay me a million Dollars.
如果他选百万的话,那我去请你去吃晚餐.
If he goes for the million, I take you to dinner.
本∶好,恐龙灭绝的主要因素是A,冰川移动,B,哺乳动物的进化, C,温室效应还是D,没人知道.呃...选B,是由于哺乳动物的进化.调查显示,没人知道.那么你问我这个问题有什么用呢,好像我知道似的.
Ben: OK, the main factor in the dinosaurs extinction was A, the movement of glaciers, B, the evolution of mammals, C, the green house effect or D, no one knows.Err...B, the evolution of mammals.Survey says, no one knows.Well then what are you asking me for, like I'm gonna know.
(在本的脑海里想起一个关于他所听到的事情的声音)
(Voices in Ben's head of things he's heard)
威特∶本,
Vito: Ben, what are you doing sitting up studying?
你还在熬夜学习?不是已经有答案了嘛.
You got the answer sheet in your pocket.
你不想上床去睡觉吗?
Doesn't that bed look mighty comfortable.
本∶我不能作弊,威特,他们抓住我了.
Ben: I can't cheat, Vito, they're on to me.
威特∶你根本就不动脑筋.你干嘛要全部都做对了.只是肯定你会错几道.
Vito: Your not thinking.You don't have to get 'em all right.Just make sure you get a couple wrong.
本∶但是我怎样做那些呢?
Ben: But how do I do that?
威特∶只是做你自己.
Vito: Just be yourself.
迈克∶他们是巫婆,本,他们是巫婆.
Mike: They're witches Ben, they're witches.
Maggie: Ben, you bring home another D in Science, you'll see a side of me
你也会见识到我的一外一面,是你从来没有看见过的一面.
you have never seen before!
开萝尔∶我情不自禁.我讨厌无知!如果我以前没有跟你提过的话,
Carol: Ben, if I haven't mentioned it before, let me mention it now;
那我就现在告诉你,你真的让我失望透顶,还有另一个有袋类动物.
you're a real disappointment to me and the other marsupials.
威特∶本,别犹豫了,作弊!
Vito: Come on Ben, cheat!
臭虫∶是,别犹豫了,本,作弊吧!
Stinky: Yeah, Ben, cheat!
杰森∶当然不可以作弊!
Jason: Of course it's not OK to cheat!
威特∶嘿,谁会知道?
Vito: Hey, who'll know?
迈克∶他们是巫婆,本.
Mike: They're witches, Ben.
臭虫∶那你还能怎么做?
Stinky: What else can you do?
开萝尔∶有袋类动物!有袋类动物!
Carol: Marsupial!Marsupial!
麦琪∶你也是只小狗.
Maggie: And your little dog too.
紧身衣女孩:一,二,三个!
Leotard Girl: And one and two and three!
本∶你是谁?
Ben: Who are you?
紧身衣女孩∶我是紧身衣店铺的女孩子,你曾经认为如果我在你的房间里的话,
Leotard Girl: Well, I'm the girl from the leotard shop who you thought
会很好.
would look good in your room.
本∶我没有大声的说出来过呀.
Ben: I never said that out loud.
Leotard Girl: Ben, you can A, wrestle with ethical dilemma of cheating
B, study the other two hundred and sixty pages that you ignored this semester
把你在这个学期所忽视的260页书再好好的学一遍,或C,看着我做有氧操.
or C, watch me aerobicise.
本∶可以选D吗?
Ben: Is there a D?
杰森∶如果你不醒醒就有了!
Jason: There will be if you don't wake up!
杰森∶本,醒醒!
Jason: Ben, wake up!
本∶爸爸,你不是女人!
Ben: Aarrghh!Dad, you're not a woman!
杰森∶不是已经好多年了.本,你还好吧?
Jason: Not for years.You OK, Ben?
本∶嗯....我想我只是被硬塞进了太多的东西,所以有点神智不清的.
Ben: Um...yeah, I guess I've just been cramming so hard, I'm delirious.
杰森∶你被塞的太满了,都睡着了.
Jason: You've bee cramming so hard, you were asleep.
本:我知道是其中之一.
Ben: Ah, well I knew it was one of the two.
杰森∶对,那么,我有什么可以帮你吗?
Jason: Yeah.So, can I help you with anything?
本:爸爸,自然科学有时候根本用不上是么?
Ben: Dad, isn't Science something you never even use in real life, anyway?
杰森∶你的问题对一个医生来说,很难回答.
Jason: Pretty tough question to ask a Doctor, Ben.
本∶哦,对不起,我老喜欢忘记你是做什么的.
Ben: Oh, right, sorry, I keep forgetting what you do.
杰森∶本,让我看看我能不能帮到你一点点.也许我可以提问你,好吗?让我们先看看这里,第一个问题是...这是作弊的条子吗?
Jason: Well let me see if I can help you a little, Ben.Maybe I can quiz you, OK?Let's take a look here, first question is...Is this a cheat sheet?
本∶错.
Ben: False.
杰森∶错.
Jason: Wrong.
本∶D,以上都不是.
Ben: D, none of the above.
杰森∶哦,本,我们刚才在楼下不是都说好了吗.
Jason: Oh, come on Ben, we went through all this downstairs.
本∶我知道,所以我不会作弊的.
Ben: I know we did and I'm not gonna cheat.
杰森∶那你为什么还留着这个?
Jason: Well then what do you still have this for?
本∶不错的问题.
Ben: Well, good question.
杰森∶恩,我希望你也能给我一个好答案.
Jason: Well, I hope you got a good answer.
本∶好,爸爸,
Ben: OK, Dad, I was originally gonna cheat.
我开始是准备要作弊的.仅仅只是因为其他的人也都会作弊.
But only because the other guys were.
杰森∶再说一次!我不管学校里其他人是否都作弊,
Jason: OK, one more time!
但是,本,
I don't care if everybody else at that school cheats Ben, you don't!'
你不可以!因为骗子从来都不会有好下场的.
Cause cheaters don't win and they always get exactly what they deserve.
本∶是先生.
Ben: Yes sir.
杰森∶现在好了,让我们忘记废话,本,
Jason: Now come on, let's go!Forget that nonsense, Ben, you can do it!
你一定可以的!努力学习,
Study hard, hit those books!Let's get the best grade you can.
解决这些书本!让我们拿到你能拿到的最好成绩.我相信你的能力!
I have faith in you!
威特∶嘿本,你决不会相信.我昨天晚上梦到穿紧身衣的女孩出现在我的房间,还做有氧操给我看.
Vito: Hey Ben, you are never gonna believe this.I dreamed that the girl from
the leotard shop showed up in my room and aerobicised for me
本∶你也是!
Ben: You too!
臭虫∶你们不会相信我做了什么梦.
Stinky: You guys aren't gonna believe the dream I had.
本∶紧身衣店里的女孩.
Ben: Girl from the leotard shop.
威特∶在你的房里做有氧操.
Vito: Aerobicising in your room.
臭虫∶不是.开萝尔穿着袋鼠衣服在我的床边责骂我.
Stinky: No.Carol's in this kangaroo suit hopping all over my bed.
威特∶臭虫,你让人觉得恶心.
Vito: Stinky, you are on sick little dude.
臭虫∶谢谢.本,你怎么也看起来像只狗一样的.
Stinky: Thanks.Ben, you look like doggy doo.
本∶当然,因为我一直学习到凌晨4点.
Ben: I should, I was up till four studying.
威特∶你为什么要学习到4点?你都已经有答案了.
Vito: Why would you study till four?You got the cheat sheet.
本∶我不会用的,可以吗?
Ben: I'm not using it, OK?
臭虫∶为什么?
Stinky: Why?
本∶我只能说,我的父母是巫婆.
Ben: Let's just say, my parents are witches.
教师∶注意,自然科学的学生.我有一些不好的消息!
Teacher: Attention, Science students.I have some bad news!
在复制室发生了一个灾难,所以...你们的试卷被毁坏了.
There was a disaster in the ditto room and...your tests have been destroyed.
学生∶耶!
Students: Yeah!
教师∶开玩笑而已.作为一个老师,
Teacher: Just kidding.I'm messing with your minds,
扰乱你们的思维,
it's one of the few joys of being a teacher.
就是其中的乐趣之一.好了,
OK, keep your eyes on your paper.
好好的看着你们自己的试卷.
Keep your arms and legs inside the car and fasten your seatbelts,
管好自己的手和脚,不要有任何的作弊行为.
it's gonna be a bumpy ride!
Ben: (In his head) Which of these four is not a marsupial
袋熊,C,负鼠,
A, kangaroo, B, wombat, C, a possum D, your sister.Oh, I'm so confused.
D,你的姐妹.我好迷惑.
Sure, they're happy now, but cheaters never win.
他们现在肯定很开心,但是,骗子是不会有好下场的.可是最后他们肯定会得A.
Eventually they're gonna get an A.
本:(在他的脑海里)妈妈,
Ben: (In his head) Mom, Dad,
爸爸,
the first thing that my report card will show you is that I didn't cheat.
首先我要在报告中告诉你们我没有欺骗.当然,
Na, I can do better than that.
我可以做的更好.
You know, I dont' think my report card is that important in light of the
我不准备在卡片上写苏联最近发生的事情.
recent events in the Soviet Union.
如果我提到苏联的话,
Na, if I mention the Soviet Union,
实事政治就会升级.
they're gonna bring up my grade in Current Events.
好,现在最好压根不提报告的事情,
OK, now the best thing to do is not to mention my report card at all;
看看会发生什么.
just keep it under my hat and try to see which way the wind blows.
我应该可以做到.
Yeah, I think I can do that.
迈克∶唷呼!本!
Mike: Yo, Benny!
本∶嘿,迈克,你在干什么?
Ben: Hey, Mike, what are you doing here?
迈克∶与我的朋友们一起吃中餐.
Mike: Having lunch with my friends.
本∶妈妈和爸爸在吗?
Ben: Are Mom and Dad around?
迈克∶啊...今天是发成绩单的日子.
Mike: Ah...report card day.
本∶你怎么知道的?
Ben: How do you know?
迈克∶嘿本,我可以闻到空气中的恐惧...像被打败的味道.
Mike: Hey Benny, I can smell the fear in the air...smells like defeat.
本∶迈克,你到底在这里做什么?
Ben: Mike, what are you doing here?
你都已经搬出去了,可是你在这里呆的时间却比我还多.过你自己的生活去吧!
You moved out and you spend more time here than I do.Get a life!
本∶没人能帮了.
Ben: Nobody can help.
迈克∶事情不像表面上的那么坏.
Mike: Look, it's never as bad as it seems.
你有足够的钱来买一张出城车票吧?
You have enough money for a bus ticket out of town?
本∶还没有差到那个地步.最少我的健康成绩是A.
Ben: It's not that bad.I got an A in health.
迈克∶本,那更糟.
Mike: Ooh, Benny that's bad.
本∶为什么?
Ben: Why?
迈克∶因为爸妈会认为只要你想学,你就一定能学好.
Mike: Because it shows 'em that you can do it if you want to.
并且这个成绩让其他成绩看起来更像痛苦的失败了.
And it makes every other grade look like a bitter failure.
本∶失败!什么失败?我的最低成绩是D.
Ben: Failures!What failures?My lowest grade is a D.
迈克∶D比F更差.
Mike: Oh, D is worse than an F.
托尼∶你怎么认为的?
Ben: How do you figure?
Mike: Alright.Well, you got an F, one line on the side makes it an
A
但是,要是D的话,就很难做了.
There aint a heck of a lot you can do with a D.
开萝尔∶大家好!恩,看起来好像是发布成绩单的日子.
Carol: Hi guys!Mmm, smells like report card day.So, is it you, Mike, or Ben?
那么是你们其中的谁呢,迈克还是本?还是你们俩?
Or is it both of you?
本∶平静下来,开萝尔,是我.
Ben: Calm down, Carol, it's just me.
开萝尔∶哦,只要你自己尽了自己最大的努力,
Carol: Oh, well as long as you did the best you could,
妈妈和爸爸不会生气的.
Mom and Dad won't get too upset.
迈克∶开萝尔,去别的地方去享受你的阳光,这个小男孩正在风中慑慑发抖呢.
Mike: Carol, go pump your sunshine some place else, OK?I mean the boy is twisting in the wind here.
杰森∶大家怎么都在这里...(流鼻涕)发放成绩单的日子.
Jason: So, how's every body this fine...(Sniffing) Report card day.
开萝尔∶我去找妈妈.
Carol: I'll get Mom.
本∶谢谢开萝尔.
Ben: Thank you Carol.
迈克∶听着本,我要跑了!
Mike: Listen Ben, I gotta run!
本∶你要走了!
Ben: You're leaving!
Mike: Yeah, well I don't want any of what's coming your way to land on
me
麦琪∶意味着,不能看电视,
Maggie: Ben, we don't get upset as long as you do your best,
放学后不能与朋友们出去闲荡.必须呆在房间里学习.
but a D is not your best and you know it.
杰森:你明年就上高中了.本,会更紧张的.我希望这两周的考试能让你明白你不可能玩一个学期然后突然就学好了.
Jason: You're starting high school next year, Ben,
it's only gonna get tougher.
I hope this two week grounding is gonna impress upon you the fact that
you cannot let a class slide all sememster and then suddenly catch up
in one night.
麦琪:也就是说,不能看电视,放学不能跟朋友玩.你要回房间学习.
Maggie: That means, no TV, no hanging out after school with your friends.You are up in your room studying.
本∶也许你们忽略了我的健康成绩--A.
Ben: Perhaps you over-looked my A in Health.
麦琪∶那只能证明如果你想做你就一定能做好.
Maggie: That only proves that you can do it if you want to.
Jason: And if you can't pull up that D on your final report card
我们不得不在暑假也把你送去学校补习.
you're gonna be doing time in summer school.
本∶嗯...你知道,我本来是可以得个A的.
Ben: Um...you know I could've gotten an A.
杰森∶靠作弊本!这是你现在要说的话?
Jason: By cheating Ben!Is that what you're brining up now?
本∶嗯...不...
Ben: Um...no...
杰森∶本,你知道骗子的下场是什么.
Jason: Come on, Ben.You know what happens to cheaters.
本∶恩,他们决不会胜利.
Ben: Yeah, yeah, they never win.
麦琪∶说对了.
Maggie: Exactly.
本∶是他们决不会胜利还是他们很少胜利?因为...
Ben: Is that rule, they never win or they hardly ever win?Because...
杰森∶你故意忽略这里的重点.我们不要再提作弊的事情,
Jason: Come on, you're missing the whole point on purpose.
我们现在谈论的是你要发挥出你的潜能!
Now forget cheating, we're talking about you working up to your potential!
威特∶唷呼!本!
Vito: Yo, Benny!
麦琪∶好了,本.
Maggie: OK, Ben, we won't embarrass you in front of your little friend.
我们不会让你在朋友的面前难堪的.去告诉威特你的惩罚马上开始,他不得不离开.
Go tell Vito that your grounding starts right now and that he has to leave.
杰森∶那个孩子怎么回事?他让你联想到谁?
Jason: Damn, what's with that kid?Who does he remind you of?
麦琪∶迈克.
Maggie: Mike.
杰森∶千真万确.当然,他的成绩还不错.
Jason: Exactly.Of course, he turned out alright.
麦琪∶不,他也不好.
Maggie: No he didn't.
本∶伙计,我...
Ben: Hi guys, look I...
威特∶我们只是想要告诉你更多的好消息;我们的父母看过成绩单后,
Vito: We just wanted to tell you more good news;
给了我们钱.
when our parents saw our report cards, they gave us money.
臭虫∶来吧,本,让我给你买个冰淇淋吃吃.
Stinky: Come on Ben, let me buy you a freezy Weezy.
本∶2个星期内,我哪里也不能去,我被罚禁闭了.
Ben: Look, I'm not going anywhere for two weeks; I'm grounded.
威特∶你这是自作自受.本来你也可以像我们一样,
Vito: Well, you got nobody to blame but yourself.
拿到好成绩的.
You could have aced that test like we did.
本∶我明白,威特,我明白.
Ben: I know Vito, I know.
臭虫∶那你为什么不那样做呢?
Stinky: So, why the heck didn't you?
本∶因为我愚不可及,当我爸跟我说骗子决不会胜利的时候,
Ben: Because I was stupid enough to believe my father when he told me
我居然会相信他.
cheaters never win.
威特∶哦,本,本,本,
Vito: Oh, Ben, Ben, Ben, where you been?Parents lie all the time.
你都在干什么?父母无时无刻不在撒谎.我的家人跟我说了一大堆根本不是那么回事的事情.
My folks told my all kinds of crazy stuff that aint true.
臭虫∶每个晚上我妈妈帮我弄被子的时候,都会说我很高.
Stinky: Every night when my Mom goes to tuck me in, she tells me I'm tall.
本∶我要走了.
Ben: Look, I gotta go.
威特∶从好的方面看.至少你现在知道了,
Vito: Look on the bright side.
当你想要事实的时候,
At least you learned that when you want the truth you come to your friends...
最好去找你的朋友们,而不是去找你爸爸.
no your old man.
本∶你说的.
Ben: You said it.
杰森∶我很庆幸我在刚刚过去的24小时的行为不会被平分.
Jason: Well, I'm glad I'm not being graded on my performance for the last twenty
four hours
麦琪∶哦!杰森,你太棒了.
Maggie: Oh, Jason, you were wonderful.
杰森∶我说的不是昨天晚上.
Jason: I'm not talking about last night.
麦琪∶我也不是.
Maggie: Neither was I.
杰森∶有一分钟吗?
Jason: Got a minute?
本∶一分钟!我相信我有2个星期的时间.
Ben: A minute!I believe I got two weeks.
杰森∶我必须向你道歉,因为我犯了一个不可原谅的错误.
Jason: Well I've got to apologise, I've made a terrible mistake.
本∶你是说我不用被关在家里了!哦,爸爸,我原谅你了.再见.
Ben: So, you mean I'm not grounded!Oh, Dad, I forgive you.See you.
杰森:不,不,等一下,
Jason: No, no, wait, wait, wait, Ben.
等一下,本.关在家里是唯一做对的事情.
Grounding you was the only thing I did right.
本∶又是老生常谈了.
Ben: Oh, so it's gonna be one of those talks.
杰森∶老生常谈!
Jason: Those talks!
本∶没什么,继续吧.
Ben: Nothing.Go on.
杰森∶我上个星期告诉你的关于作弊的忠告,是...错的.
Jason: Well, the...advice I gave you last week about cheating Ben, was...wrong.
本∶肯定是.
Ben: Sure was.
杰森∶我不是说它错,而是说它不够完整.
Jason: I'm not saying it was wrong...it was incomplete.
本∶又是老生常谈了.
Ben: Oh, so it is gonna be one of those talks.
杰森∶本,不要像小孩子似的撅嘴了.
Jason: Ben, don't pout like a kid.
我把你当成成人一样的来和你谈的.我告诉你骗子从不会胜利的时候,
Come on, I'm trying to talk to you as an adult.
本,我以为这些就是你必须知道的了.
Look, when I told you cheaters never win, Ben,
但是,事实上,
I thought that was all you needed to know.
还有很多东西需要知道,因为骗子有时也会胜利.
But there is a lot more to it, because cheaters do win.
本∶他们不只胜利,他们还赢了现金.
Ben: Not only do they win, they win cash.
杰森∶有时甚至比钱更大.有时可以在奥运会上赢得金牌;有的甚至能赢得白宫.
Jason: Sometimes it's even bigger than that.
Sometimes they win gold medals at the Olympics;
on a rare occasion they even win the White House.
本∶爸爸,我不明白.
Ben: Dad, I'm not following this.
我是说如果你可以通过作弊,获得侥幸成功,那作弊有什么不对呢?
I mean, if you can cheat, and get away with it, then what's wrong with it?
杰森:本,你看待作弊的方式,
Jason: Ben, the way you see cheating really depends on how you see the
很大程度上取决于你看待世界的方式.
whole world.
Ben: I don't understand it at all.I got a D in Science, remember
杰森∶本,我们为什么要生活在地球上,
Jason: Look...why are we on this earth, Ben?What's the point of our lives.
而我们人生的意义又是什么?我们必须做出选择,
You know, I mean we all have to make a choice,
你是想用有条理的眼光来看待世界呢,还是想用混乱的眼光来看.
you either see things as order or chaos.
如果你选择用混乱的眼光来看的话,人生也就根本没有任何意义了.
And if you see the world as chaos, then there's no point in life at all.
因为什么都不重要了.我们只不过是一群四处逃窜的人,
You know, nothing matters.
互相撞击,玩,
We're all just a bunch of people running around we're bumping into each
制造噪音,一直到我们死去的那天.
other, having fun, making noises till we die.
我们只是在占用空间,本,
We're just taking up space, Ben, and I can't believe in that.
我都无法相信这些.但是,
Well look, if you see...
如果你...如果你用有条理的眼光来看世界的话,
if you see the world as having order, Ben,
本,一切事情都有理由了.
then there's a reason to everything.
有理由要在早晨起床,有理由要好好的利用你的人生;有理由去学习,
There's a reason to get up in the morning,
本,这样的话,
there's a reason to make something of your life;
所有的一切都联系在一起了.如果学习是很重要的,
there's a reason for learning, Ben, it all fits together.
那么本,作弊就是不对的了.
And if learning is important, Ben, then cheating is wrong.
本∶就算侥幸成功也是错的?
Ben: Even when you get away with it?
杰森∶什么是侥幸成功?
Jason: What's getting away with it?
本∶没有被抓住.
Ben: Not getting caught.
杰森∶什么意思?
Jason: Which means?
本∶得了个A.
Ben: Getting an A.
杰森∶那A又意味着什么呢?
Jason: So does what does the A mean?
本∶十元!
Ben: Ten Bucks!
杰森∶难道10元钱就意味着你已经学到知识了吗?
Jason: So what does it mean you've learned?
本∶什么都没有学到!
Ben: Nothing!
杰森∶所以你作弊后,什么都没有得到!
Jason: Well then you've been cheating for nothing!
本∶是的!
Ben: Yes!
杰森∶重点是什么?
Jason: What's the point in it?
本∶必须要有个重点吗?
Ben: Does there have to be a point?
杰森∶是的本,否则就是一片混乱了!
Jason: Yes Ben, or there's chaos!
本:所以,总是要有重点.
Ben: So, you're saying there should be point in what I'm doing all the time!
杰森∶是的.
Jason: Yes.
本∶我认为我没有被当成一个成年人一样来谈话.
Ben: I don't think I like being talked to as an adult.
杰森∶有时没有一个人会.
Jason: Well sometimes none of us do.
本∶爸爸,有人会真的愿意给这个混乱一个公平的机会吗?
Ben: Dad, has anyone really given this chaos thing a fair chance?
杰森∶迈克已经越来越明白了.你明白了一点点吗?
Jason: Mike came close.Are you getting any of this?
本∶我开始有点明白,骗子是真的不会赢,但是呢,我无法解释.
Ben: Ah, well, I'm starting to realise that cheaters really don't win, but I couldn't explain it.
杰森∶呵呵,那你现在的感觉就像2个星期以前一样,
Jason: Well then you're exactly where I was two weeks ago when I couldn't
我当时也无法跟你解释.
explain it to you.
本:等等……如果真的能学到东西的话,
Ben: Wait a minute...
我每天晚上都写作业,
if the point of school's really learning stuff,
我会一直学习,
then I gotta do homework every night, and I gotta study all the time,
我要……
and I gotta be...
杰森∶等等.别急,
Jason: W...w...wait, wait, hold on, one step at a time, Ben.
一步一步来,本.
I don't want you exploding on me.Look...
我可不想你在我身上爆发.我想让你意识到,本,
what I want you to realise,
现在是该你做出选择的时候了,是有条理还是混乱.
Ben is that it's time for you to make a choice...order or chaos.
不过,我想我们有了第一次的成年人间的谈话.
Well, I think we've had our first adult conversation.
本∶没错.你能不能答应我,
Ben: Yeah.We did, didn't we?
下次的谈话不要这么久?
Do you promise we don't have to have another one for a real long time?
杰森∶成交.
Jason: Deal.
本∶爸爸,通过这次谈话后,我是不是可以恢复自由了?
Ben: Dad, is there any chance that our conversation means I'm not grounded any more
杰森∶不可能.
Jason: No chance at all.
本∶只是问问.如果说每件事情都有重点的话,
Ben: Just checking.If there's a point to every thing,
也许当穿紧身衣的金发碧眼的女人再来时,
maybe that blonde woman in the leotard will be back,
我可以告诉她一些关于条理的事情...比如说遵循它们...
and I can teach her something about order...like following 'em.
杰森:不行,本.
本∶值得一试.
00:21:36,600
Jason: No Ben. Ben: Worth a shot.